
export const quizQuestions_2 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'How does the || (OR) operator work in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'It returns true if both operands are true.',
        'It returns true if either operand is true.',
        'It returns false if both operands are false.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It returns true if either operand is true.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the || (OR) operator return if the first operand is truthy?',
      choices: [
        'The first operand.',
        'The second operand.',
        'A boolean value.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'The first operand.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which operator in JavaScript can be used for short-circuit evaluation?',
      choices: [
        '|| (OR) operator',
        '&& (AND) operator',
        '?? (Nullish Coalescing) operator',
        'All of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: true || false?',
      choices: [
        'true',
        'false',
        'null',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'true'
    },
    {
      question: 'How does the && (AND) operator behave in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'It returns true if both operands are true.',
        'It returns true if either operand is true.',
        'It returns false if both operands are false.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It returns true if both operands are true.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the && (AND) operator return if the first operand is falsy?',
      choices: [
        'The first operand.',
        'The second operand.',
        'A boolean value.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'The first operand.'
    },
    {
      question: 'How does the ?? (Nullish Coalescing) operator differ from || (OR) operator?',
      choices: [
        'The ?? operator only returns the second operand if the first operand is null or undefined.',
        'The ?? operator only returns true if both operands are true.',
        'The ?? operator only returns false if both operands are false.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'The ?? operator only returns the second operand if the first operand is null or undefined.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: null ?? 5?',
      choices: [
        'null',
        '5',
        'true',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '5'
    },
    {
      question: 'In JavaScript, what is the purpose of using the short-circuiting logic?',
      choices: [
        'To simplify code by reducing the number of if statements.',
        'To optimize code for better performance.',
        'To handle null or undefined values more efficiently.',
        'All of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the expression: true && "Hello" return in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'true',
        '"Hello"',
        'false',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '"Hello"'
    },
  ]  
}